Hey, what are you guys
looking at?
Oh, it's a poster
for that World War I movie
that I'm in.
Check it out.
Yeah?
Wow, it looks
really violent.
Uh-huh.
I know.
I'm coming soon
to a theater near you.
I'm in THX.
I'm unsuitable
for children.
Man, I cannot wait
to see this.
Yeah, yeah, it's already
generating Oscar buzz.
I started that.
I thought I did.
Oh, hey, guess what?
I just talked to my agent,
and the premiere is next week
and you're all invited.
( gasps )
That's great.
Are we going
to take a limo?
Sure, why not?
I love taking limos
when nobody died.
Well, obviously,
I won't be able to come.
For those of you who haven't
checked their calendars
today's my due date.
Well, you know
I just want to
take a moment and
thank you guys
for how great you've
been during this time.
I really couldn't have
done it without you.
And I have loved
these last nine months.
And even though I am so
looking forward to the next part
I am really going to miss
being pregnant.
That's right,
still no baby.
Come on, people
please make some room.
Uh, sweetie, maybe you'd
be more comfortable here.
( deep sigh )
You.
Like you haven't done enough.
Look, I know how
miserable you are.
I wish there was
something I could do.
I mean, I wish I
were a sea horse.
Because with sea horses
it's the male...
they carry the babies.
And then also, um, I'd
be far away in the sea.
Oh, God.
( moans )
I have never been
so uncomfortable
in my entire life.
Oh, I know, I've been there.
I remember toward the end...
Oh, Phoebe,
that's a great story.
Could you tell it to me while
you're getting me some iced tea?
( groans )
Oh, God...
Get out!
Get out, get out, get out!
Let's.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
( groans )
Hey, did you have
the baby yet?
Do you want me to come
over there and sit on you?
'Cause I'll do it.
What are you doing here
so early?
They sent me home
from work.
They were, like
"Start your maternity leave now.
Just rest.
Get ready for the baby."
Well, you know what? Screw 'em.
They don't want me there, I'll
just hang out with you guys.
Or you could do volunteer work.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Joey, it's Estelle. Great news.
I was able to get you and one
guest tickets to your premiere.
One guest? You told me
I could have six tickets.
Well, I sold four of them
on eBay.
( groans )
You'll be sitting
next to HotGuy372.
Oh, my God. So that's it?
I only get to bring one guest?
Yeah, what time do you want
to pick me up?
Hello?
Did you hear that?
I only get one extra ticket
to my premiere.
So somehow I have to pick
between you three and Ross.
Wait. Wh-What about me?
Well, you said you
didn't want to go.
I don't, but I would still
like to be acknowledged.
What, just because I'm pregnant,
I'm invisible?
Definitely not invisible.
Well, you know, Ross didn't
care enough to be here
so I think he's out.
You know, you snooze, you lose.
He's not snoozing;
he's teaching a class.
Well, then somebody's snoozing.
And, Joey, not that this
should affect you at all
but, um, if you were to pick me
I was planning on wearing
a sequin dress cut down to here.
I haven't seen this dress.
Star in a movie.
Joey, you pick whoever
you want, okay?
You just listen to your heart.
What does it tell you?
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
Well, uh...
I think I want to take Chandler.
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe,
Phoebe, Phoebe...
( imitating flat-line tone )
You really want to take me?
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I'm sorry,
I wish I could take everybody
but, you know, Chandler's
always supported my career.
He's paid for acting classes
and headshots and stuff
and, well, this would be my way
of paying you back.
So, you're never actually going
to pay me back?
Hey, just because he
paid for your headshots
you're going to take him?
Joey, I don't think
you're comprehending
just how slutty
this dress is.
It's not just the stuff
he paid for.
I mean, it's-it's everything,
you know?
He... he read lines with me.
He went with me on auditions
when I was really nervous.
And then he consoled me
after I didn't get parts
that I really wanted.
You always believed in me, man.
Even-even when I didn't believe
in myself.
I always knew
you were going to make it.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks. That...
that means a lot to me.
Mon, maybe one of these guys
wants to wear your dress.
All right,
I'm going to go shave.
( clears throat )
Yeah, well,
I'm going to go, uh, spit.
( Rachel groans )
Oh, I have to pee.
If I don't come out
in five minutes
it's because
I've choked to death
on the potpourri stink.
When she comes out
you hold her nose,
I'll blow in her mouth
and the kid will just
( pops ) right out of her.
She's over a week late.
She's got to have it
today, right?
I don't know.
I think it's still
going to be a while.
Mmm. Care to make
it interesting?
I bet you that she'll have it
by this time tomorrow.
You're on.
Okay, how much?
$100,000.
How about 50 bucks?
Fine. I'll call Zurich
and move some money around.
RACHEL:
All right, whose turn is it
to help me get up?
( clears throat )
No one's here!
Oh, damn it.
( cheering and applause )
This is so exiting.
So glamorous--
people taking our picture.
GIRL:
Joey!
How do I look?
A little tall.
What?
Do you mind crouching
down a little bit
so I look taller?
( cheering continues )
There you go.
It's just so glamorous.
GIRL:
I love you, Joey!
( groans )
Oh, hey, Mon,
Rach is here.
And you're still pregnant.
( Rachel continues groaning )
Oh, I'm sorry.
I know how uncomfortable
you are.
You know what?
You look great.
Oh...
Yeah, like 50 bucks.
Oh, I have to go pee.
Apparently, this baby thinks
that my bladder
is a squeeze toy.
Oh, damn it. Damn it.
Here's your 50 bucks.
That's interesting
that you lost.
Now, I forget,
do you like to lose?
All right, stop it.
Double or nothing
that she has it by tomorrow.
Fine. You're on.
Okay.
Until then, General Grant
why don't you set up camp
right there.
Hey, is Rachel here?
We have a doctor's appointment.
She's in the bathroom.
Rach, we got to go.
RACHEL:
In a minute!
People ask me
why we're not together.
I just don't know
what to tell them.
RACHEL:
All right,
all right
let's go.
ROSS:
Uh, do you want
to go change first?
Doctor's keeping
the office open
late for us
but if you hurry...
No, I'm fine.
Really? You don't think
that's a little inappropriate?
What?
Good God, man,
don't anger it.
Ross, it is 100 degrees outside.
For the first time in weeks,
I am somewhat comfortable.
Fine, fine,
you know what?
Whatever you want, okay?
You're the mommy.
Uh-uh-uh, pal.
Don't call me mommy.
It's bad enough
you call your own mother that.
I'm actually with her
on this one.
JOEY ( in movie ):
I thought I knew
who the enemy was,
but it was you all along.
You led them right to us,
didn't you?
Okay, this is it-- this is
my big fight scene coming up.
...but I'm fighting for every
man in the 82nd Ground Division.
Ross?
Yeah?
Can I ask
you something?
Uh-huh.
When Carol was pregnant
with Ben...
Mm-hmm.
Were you this irritating?
Wow.
Excuse me?
Uh, nothing, nothing.
You were just, uh...
you've been a little short
with me lately.
I'm not trying to irritate you.
Well, then you just must have
a natural talent for it.
You know what?
The doctor will be in soon.
Why don't we not speak
until then.
Okay.
( sighs )
Seriously, breathe louder, Ross.
That's great.
You know, we should probably
ask the doctor
if she even knows how
to deliver a baby
that's half human,
half pure evil.
Hello.
Hi, Dr. Long,
how are you?
Oh, you're nice to her.
She has the drugs.
We'll do a quick check.
Okay.
So, eight days late, huh?
Yeah.
You must be getting
a little uncomfortable.
Yeah, just a tad.
Well, you're about 80% effaced,
so you're on your way.
It still could last
a little while longer.
If you're anxious, there are
a few ways to help things along.
Do them.
Actually they are things
that you can do.
Just some home remedies.
But in my experience,
I've found that
some of them are
very effective.
Well, we are ready
to try anything.
Okay, there's an herbal
tea you can drink.
You can take
some castor oil.
There's eating spicy foods.
Great. We will
do all of those.
Taking a long walk.
Good. Done.
And there's the one that's
proved most effective: sex.
You've got to be kidding me.
Good job, Joe.
Well done. Top-notch.
You liked it?
You really liked it?
Oh, yeah!
Well, which part exactly?
The whole thing!
Can't we go?
Oh, no, no, no.
Hold it. Give me
some specifics.
I loved the specifics.
The specifics were
the best part!
Hey, what about the scene
with the kangaroo?
Did you... did you like
that part?
I was surprised to see
a kangaroo...
in a World War I epic.
You fell asleep!
There was no kangaroo.
They didn't take
any of my suggestions.
Thanks a lot
for coming, buddy.
See you later.
Don't go. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Look! This guy
fell asleep!
He fell asleep, too!
Be mad at him!
Or... call an ambulance.
Hey.
Hi!
What did
the doctor say?
Any news on when the
baby's going to come?
No. But she did
give us some ideas
on how to induce labor.
Yeah. We tried them all.
We went for a walk.
Uh, we tried special tea,
castor oil, spicy food.
Nothing has worked.
Well, there is one thing
that we didn't try
but someone thinks that
that will open up
a can of worms.
Well, what is it? What is it?
If it's going to help
bring the baby here
like, today, I mean,
I think you should do it.
It's sex.
Do it!
Monica...
I'm just saying it's been
a really long time for you.
I mean, women have needs.
Do it. Get yours.
Oh, I... I don't know
about that.
No, I think
if the two of you had sex
the, the, the repercussions
would be catastrophic.
All right, let's be practical.
If Ross isn't willing to do it
I mean, he's not the only guy
in the world
you can have sex with.
You could borrow Chandler.
Chandler is good!
Monica, what is
the matter with you?
Nothing. I just want the baby
to be born today.
Why? Why today?
Okay, fine.
I keep betting Phoebe that
you're going to have the baby
and... I don't want
to lose again.
What?!
While she's been
going through this hell
you've been making money?
You're betting on your friend
staying in this misery?
I'll take that bet.
What?!
Well, I'm miserable here.
I may as well make
some money out of it.
Can I get some
of that action?
Wait a minute.
Now I'm betting against
all three of you?
Oh, honey, don't worry--
I really do feel
like tomorrow it's
going to happen.
Oh, okay.
( no audio )
( door opens )
Hey.
Sleeping beauty.
Where have you been?
I tried to call you.
I want to talk to you.
I still feel so bad.
( baby talk ):
Oh, no! Were you upset?
Did you lose sleep?
I'm so sorry.
Look, the only reason
I came over here
is to settle things
between us, okay?
You've done a lot for me
and my career.
I wanted to pay you back
by taking you to the premiere
but you missed it!
Okay, so, how much do I owe ya?
What?!
Give me a number.
I don't want
to owe you anything.
You don't
owe me anything.
I don't want your...
Ah-ah-ah! We're doing this.
Okay, now you got me
my first set of
head shots, right?
How much were those?
I don't know.
Uh... $500.
Okay, $500. What else?
Well, then there was
the second set...
the infamous "booger"
head shots.
Okay, so that's another $500.
That's $500 and $500...
( muttering softly )
You want a calculator?
Please.
Here.
Oh. Okay. All right,
what else?
Well, uh, there's
acting classes
stage combat classes...
tap classes...
Which we're still keeping
under our hats.
Uh, then there was
that dialect coach
who helped you with the play
where you needed
a Southern accent.
Which, after 20 hours of lessons
still came out Jamaican.
What the hell
are you talking about?
( Jamaican accent ):
Da South will rise again, mon.
Yes. Money well spent.
Okay, what else? Rent.
Okay. Uh, two, three years
of rent, utilities, food.
Okay, okay.
So I'm writing you
a check for...
So you fell asleep
during my movie.
Big deal, right?
How do you clear
this thing?
Come on.
Finish your enchilada.
Ah... Ross, we've tried
all the spicy food.
It's not working.
Okay, here. Have one
of these peppers.
Oh... oh-ha!
Oh, God. So hot.
Oh, my God...
( whimpering )
By the way, you don't want
to touch the pepper
and then touch
your eye.
I am feeling nothing.
Oh... oh...
( whimpering continues )
Speaking of hot
watching you do that
really makes me want
to have sex with you.
Stop it.
Oh, come on, Ross!
Why are we wasting our time
with all this other stuff?
We know it's going to work.
It's doctor-recommended!
I'm sorry
but we have to have
some boundaries.
Oh...!
My God, I'm dying.
Oh, come on, Ross!
I mean, we've done it before,
we'll do it again.
It'll be a nice way
to bookend the pregnancy!
This is insane!
I'm not going to make
love to you
just so you'll go
into labor.
"Make love"?
What are you, a girl?
Always a great way
to get into a man's pants.
What? You would be performing
a service, okay?
Just think of me as, like,
a ketchup bottle.
You know, sometimes you have
to bang on the end of it
just to get something
to come out.
I love when you talk
dirty to me.
Ugh. I know it. You're right.
That's not sexy.
Oh... oh...
Whoops! Oh, I seem
to have dropped my fork.
Let me just bend over
and get it.
Oh, God!
( groaning )
Okay, enough!
This is not going
to happen.
Oh, come on, Ross.
I'm miserable here.
Come on, you started this.
Now you finish it.
Come on, wuss.
Make love to me.
You know what?
What?
Forget it.
Oh, well, what now, Ross?
You're not going to talk?
How on earth will you
ever annoy me?
Oh, wait a minute.
I know.
( snores )
I mean, you'd think
the damn jalapeño
would have cleared up
your sinuses, but no!
That's not enough...
What are you doing?
I'm getting that baby
out of you!
Oh, God!
Oh, I know...
Oh, no, no...
Oh... I think my water
just broke.
I am good!
Okay, okay, I got the pillow...
uh, I got the bag.
You got the keys?
I got the keys.
Okay, okay.
( laughing )
Hey...
Yeah?
We're having a baby.
I didn't, uh, really
have time to read
this part of the books
but do you think
we have time...?
Not so much.
Okay.
$200
-Thank you.
That's it. I'm done.
I don't care when the baby
comes-- no more betting.
Okay.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Okay.
I guess we can bet
one more time.
Is Rachel having the baby?
How did you know that?!
Joey, Chandler! It's time!
They're at the coffeehouse.
You know everything!
Oh, wait...
double or nothing.
I bet you the baby
is over seven pounds.
I bet you it has hair!
I bet you it's a girl.
We know it's a girl.
I'll give you really
good odds.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org